(this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]=this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]||[]).push([[0],{24:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F","correct_answer":"Dirk%20the%20Daring","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F","correct_answer":"Homo%20Sapiens","incorrect_answers":["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Books","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F","correct_answer":"Bilius","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F","correct_answer":"Robert%20Kirkman","incorrect_answers":["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F","correct_answer":"Electric%20Company","incorrect_answers":["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F","correct_answer":"Kingston","incorrect_answers":["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20","correct_answer":"1962","incorrect_answers":["1492","1963","1987"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F","correct_answer":"%2412.7%20Billion","incorrect_answers":["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F","correct_answer":"55","incorrect_answers":["50","60","54"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F","correct_answer":"Alonsus%20Faol","incorrect_answers":["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F","correct_answer":"Coils","incorrect_answers":["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F","correct_answer":"Vanilla","incorrect_answers":["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.","correct_answer":"Poland%20and%20Lithuania","incorrect_answers":["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F","correct_answer":"George%20Clooney","incorrect_answers":["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F","correct_answer":"Plastic%20Beach","incorrect_answers":["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F","correct_answer":"No%20Mercy","incorrect_answers":["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F","correct_answer":"Hong%20Kong","incorrect_answers":["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]')},45:function(e,t,r){},46:function(e,t,r){},51:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var n=r(2),a=r(0),i=r.n(a),o=r(11),s=r.n(o),c=(r(45),r.p,r(46),r(12)),l=r(13),u=r(16),h=r(14),d=r(24),p=r(70),m=r(71),y=r(72),f=r(73),g=r(74),b=function(e){Object(u.a)(r,e);var t=Object(h.a)(r);function r(e){var n;return Object(c.a)(this,r),(n=t.call(this,e)).state={},n}return Object(l.a)(r,[{key:"render",value:function(){console.log("Props",this.props);var e=0;return"hard"==this.props.rat?e=3:"easy"==this.props.rat?e=1:"medium"==this.props.rat&&(e=2),Object(n.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(n.jsx)("h3",{children:this.props.cat.toString().replace(/%20/g," ")}),Object(n.jsx)(g.a,{name:"read-only",value:e,readOnly:!0}),Object(n.jsx)("h3",{children:this.props.question})]})}}]),r}(a.Component),w=function(e){Object(u.a)(r,e);var t=Object(h.a)(r);function r(e){var n;return Object(c.a)(this,r),(n=t.call(this,e)).checkans=function(e){e==n.props.data.correct_answer?(n.setState({lbl:"Correct..!"}),n.props.cr_Func(!0)):(n.setState({lbl:"Incorrect."}),n.props.cr_Func(!1)),n.props.isnext(!0)},n.state={lbl:""},n}return Object(l.a)(r,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;console.log(this.props.isDisa);this.state.isdisabled;var t=this.props.data.question,r=this.props.data.incorrect_answers;return r.push(this.props.data.correct_answer),Object(n.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(n.jsx)(b,{rat:this.props.data.difficulty,cat:this.props.data.category,question:t.toString().replace(/%20/g," ").replace(/%3F/g,"?")}),r.map((function(t,r){return Object(n.jsx)("div",{children:Object(n.jsx)(f.a,{variant:"contained",color:"primary",disabled:e.props.dis,onClick:function(r){return e.checkans(t)},children:t.toString().replace(/%20/g," ")},r)})})),Object(n.jsx)("h1",{children:this.state.lbl})]})}}]),r}(a.Component),j=r(75),_=function(e){Object(u.a)(r,e);var t=Object(h.a)(r);function r(e){var n;return Object(c.a)(this,r),(n=t.call(this,e)).setNext=function(){n.setState({Stepper:n.state.Stepper+1,btndis:!n.state.btndis})},n.getScore=function(e){e?n.setState({countCorrect:n.state.countCorrect+1}):n.setState({countWrong:n.state.countWrong+1})},n.showbtn=function(e){n.setState({btndis:e})},n.state={questions:d.map((function(e){return e.question.replace(/%20/g," ").replace(/%3F/,"?")})),C_Answer:d.map((function(e){return e.correct_answer})),Stepper:1,countCorrect:0,countWrong:0,btndis:!1},n}return Object(l.a)(r,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this.state,t=e.countWrong,r=e.countCorrect/t*100;return Object(n.jsx)("div",{style:{margin:"20px"},children:this.state.Stepper<20?Object(n.jsxs)(p.a,{container:!0,spacing:3,children:[Object(n.jsxs)(p.a,{item:!0,xs:12,children:[Object(n.jsx)(m.a,{variant:"determinate",value:5*this.state.Stepper,style:{height:"20px"}}),Object(n.jsxs)("h3",{children:["Question ",this.state.Stepper," of ",this.state.questions.length]}),Object(n.jsx)(y.a,{children:Object(n.jsx)(w,{isnext:this.showbtn,dis:this.state.btndis,cr_Func:this.getScore,data:d[this.state.Stepper]})}),Object(n.jsxs)("h5",{children:["Score ",r,"%"]}),Object(n.jsxs)(j.a,{children:[Object(n.jsx)(j.a,{striped:!0,variant:"success",now:0},1),Object(n.jsx)(j.a,{variant:"warning",now:r},2),Object(n.jsx)(j.a,{striped:!0,variant:"danger",now:0},3)]})]}),Object(n.jsx)(f.a,{onClick:this.setNext,disabled:this.state.btnnext,children:"NEXT"}),Object(n.jsx)("br",{}),Object(n.jsx)("br",{})]}):Object(n.jsx)("h1",{children:"Good Luck"})})}}]),r}(a.Component);var O=function(){return Object(n.jsx)("div",{children:Object(n.jsx)(_,{})})},x=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&r.e(3).then(r.bind(null,76)).then((function(t){var r=t.getCLS,n=t.getFID,a=t.getFCP,i=t.getLCP,o=t.getTTFB;r(e),n(e),a(e),i(e),o(e)}))};s.a.render(Object(n.jsx)(i.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(n.jsx)(O,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),x()}},[[51,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.2a2179b2.chunk.js.map